wicr.me 2019-04-06

# Privacy Policy

* * *

In order to extend protection to the privacy and rights of our clients and site visitors, we have created a Privacy Policy that sets forth what information Wi.cr collects on visitors and what is done with the collected information. This Privacy Policy directs the way in which we collect, use, maintain and disclose information gathered from users of this website (each, a “User”).

## **Privacy**

Wi.cr values the privacy of Users. It is our commitment to protect the information entrusted to us by Users.

## **What We Collect**

With the use of online forms for ordering products and services, Wi.cr collects personally identifiable information from Users. We may also gather information as to how Users make use of our site. For instance, we may track the number of unique views acquired by the pages of the site or the domains from which Users come from. “Cookies” are used by Wi.cr so that we can track how Users use our site.

## **What we do with the Information**

Personally identifiable information gathered through our site may be used to (a) contact Users and inform them about products and services offered by Wi.cr and its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners, and (b) to enhance User experience with Wi.cr and our affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. The users’ database of Wi.cr will never be sold to any entity for purposes of marketing or mailing lists. Personal information will not be sold or otherwise transferred to our business partners without us obtaining prior consent; however, when, in our good faith judgment, we are obliged to do so under pertinent laws, we will reveal collected information to third parties.
